

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



github.com/Gazwai

✓ garyyau080@gmail.com

I am a Tokyo-based full stack developer, originally from England. I have experience with Ruby, JavaScript, SQL, HTML, CSS, Figma, and AJAX. I am a big fan of Ruby and Ruby on Rails due to Ruby's clean syntax, RuR's opinionated MVC pattern which is easy to understand and implement and TDD tools like Rspec.

I have recently been using React and I'm implementing it into my projects due to the reusability of components and its virtual dom. All of which makes me excited. as it will speed up development and loading times.

SKILLS



Languages: Ruby, Javascript, SQL

Technologies: Ruby on Rails, React, Redux, Postgresql, Git, Heroku, Figma, Bootstrap, AJAX

EXPERIENCE



Mamoru - Frontend developer

April 2022 - Present

- Volunteer frontend developer working on Mamoru web app dealing with bug fixes, features and testing in React, JEST, React testing Library, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Collaborate in a large team with weekly meetings held for task delegation and discussion.

Le Wagon Tokyo - Teaching Assistant

March 2022 - Present

Assistant Teacher to multiple classes of students. Teaching Ruby, Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS,
JavaScript, SQL, and best practices for writing clean code.

Berkeley House - English Instructor

April 2017 - Present

PROJECTS



Chirpy

- A **Ruby on Rails** app designed for parents to shield their children from being exposed to negative content with help from IBM's Tone Analyzer API.
- Lead developer on the Chirpy **chrome extension** that sends content from the DOM and receives a response from the Chirpy API using **JavaScript**, **Fetch API** and **JSON**.

Two Bridal

A Ruby on Rails marketplace app for finding and hiring wedding dresses.

EDUCATION



Le Wagon Web Development Bootcamp

September 2021 - March 2022

24-week part-time Coding Bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Figma, git, Github, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

Nottingham Trent University

September 2010 - July 2013

LL.B. Bachelors of Laws Honours